[Ninako Kinoshita]
[Ren Ichinose]
[Ren's on the same train as me!]
[He's so close! Super asleep, too!]
Now arriving at Shin-Sakuta.
I'm so sorry. Let me buy you a new one.
Hello?
It's fine! That keychain was from ages ago anyway.
Then it's practically irreplaceable now, no?
The train will soon be departing.
It's no big deal, really.
This is my stop.
What class and year are you?
At school.
I'm a first year, in Class 1. My name is Ninako Kinoshita.
Guys, guys! Big news!
[Episode 1]
Ren rejected another girl.
Again? How many does that make it now?
That's the sixth confession he's shot down so far.
Some of those girls were notoriously cute, too.
[Sayuri Uehara]
Maybe he already has a girlfriend?
[Tamaki Tsutsui]
Not as far as I know.
Speaking of, look!
As cool and suave as ever.
Sure, he's good-looking.
But doesn't he also seem a bit standoffish?
I don't think that's necessarily true.
Just yesterday, he...
Hey, what happened to your keychain, Ninako?
[Daiki Korenaga]
The one you had on since middle school.
Oh, that? It broke off.
You're not even her boyfriend. How'd you notice?
Someone's a bit too observant of Ninako.
A-Am not.
Yamada, great timing. The other day...
You're such an open book.
This is getting hard to watch. Just confess to him already.
Huh?
You like him too, don't you?
Sure, Daiki and I have been good friends since middle school.
He's a nice guy, and easy to talk to, too.
Exactly. That's what you'd call "love".
It is?
- Should we get back to our seats?
- Yeah.
Great timing.
I was just on my way to your classroom.
I couldn't find anything similar, but...
Here.
Since I broke that keychain of yours.
It really wasn't that big of a deal though.
Ninako.
Could I see your English homework?
Sure.
See you.
Thanks.
That keychain's not really your style, is it?
- Shut up.
- It's way too girly.
- Just drop it.
- What? I'm just saying.
Yup, I hear you.
The train will be arriving shortly.
Please stand behind the yellow lines.
Mind if I take the seat next to you?
Go ahead.
Now that I think about it, I've never seen him smile before.
I wonder what he'd look like with a grin on his face.
Kinoshita.
You don't need to put that thing on if it's not your style.
Everyone's got their own tastes, so I'd take no offense.
This keychain isn't just some "thing".
If someone goes out of their way for me,
of course I'd appreciate the favor.
So this keychain stays on.
Besides, it's my possession now.
Don't treat it like some kind of junk!
Weirdo.
[Sixteen: Teens Summer Fashion Collection]
[The Girly-Girl's Favorite, Blush Nails!]
Say, Ninako. Do you also think Ichinose's good-looking?
I guess so.
See, look at this girl here.
You'd say this model is objectively cute, right?
That's how it is with Ren.
It's not like I have a crush on him or anything.
Huh?
My chest hurts.
I see.
By the way, that model is my older sister.
- What?
- I'm supposed to keep it on the down-low,
but I figure you two will cross paths soon anyway.
Now my chest feels heavy.
- Dude, watch out!
- Huh?
Sorry!
It's fine.
I shouldn't have been spacing out.
No, I should've watched where I was going.
[Manabu Miyoshi]
[Yutaro Terada]
That's the bell. Run off to class, you two.
I'm really sorry.
Take care.
You've got something on your mind, don't you?
[Hoshina Chiaki: School nurse]
It's written all over your face.
I just felt bad for causing that guy trouble by getting hurt.
Is that all you're worried about?
Sir, I apparently like someone.
Huh?
At least, my friend says so. And I trust her word on these things.
Here, try one.
It's good.
Thank you.
Gross!
Right? It's "Offal Barbecue" flavored candy.
You should learn to doubt a bit more, Kinoshita.
And done.
They're so shiny, they look almost appetizing!
You weren't ever interested in dolling yourself up.
Romance is finally on the mind, huh?
I'm not entirely sure yet.
What does "love" feel like?
Love is when your chest squeezes
just thinking about your crush.
Love is suffocating,
and can make you tearful, too.
Love can also be painful. Like you've taken a stab to the heart.
What? Love hurts?
I'm not seeing any redeeming qualities.
Love hurts, but it's not a bad feeling.
Your nails look adorable.
Kinoshita.
Take this seat.
But...
You hurt your leg today, didn't you?
Thanks.
[Takumi Ando]
[SR-Line Route Map]
Now arriving at Shin-Sakuta.
Ren, this is your stop.
Ren?
Wake up, the doors are closing.
Wake up!
I missed my stop.
I tried to wake you up.
You did?
Thanks.
I already missed my stop. Might as well walk you back.
Just because our parents are divorced,
doesn't mean we have to drift apart, too.
Yeah, yeah. I already heard you the first thousand times.
Then we're on the same page? Good.
Don't tell me you're this clingy with your boyfriend too.
Am not.
Careful, or he'll come to hate you, Mayuka.
We're a lovey-dovey couple, thank you very much.
[Mayuka Korenaga]
I admit, I haven't seen him recently
with the job and college entrance exams coming up.
But we text and call every day to make up for it.
Maybe you're the only one who thinks everything is okay.
Someone's in a bad mood today.
Wonder who that could be.
Let me guess. Things aren't going well with your crush?
If you don't confess first, someone else will take her, you know.
Lean on me, I can take it.
My bad.
It's fine.
I'm glad I spruced up my nails today.
Thanks for walking me back.
Did I make your shoulder sore?
Well, you certainly leaned on me with everything you had.
S-Sorry.
I'm joking.
I think I've been hit enough times today.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you.
"I've been hit enough times today"?
Wake up, the doors are closing.
Ren?
He was awake the whole time.
It's not a bad feeling at all.
Ninako, I've liked you for a long time now.
You were my anchor
when my parents were going through their divorce.
I've had a crush on you since then.
Will you go out with me?
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Do you have a crush on Ichinose?
How did you...
That guy has a girlfriend, you know.
What?
He's dating my older sister.
Has been for a while now.
Loving him won't get you anywhere.
Even if Ren has a girlfriend,
my feelings for him won't just disappear.
I'm such an idiot.
If only I acted sooner.
Maybe then things would've been different.
But I get it.
Just because the girl I love is crushing on another guy,
doesn't mean my feelings will disappear. Right?
Man, I can't believe myself.
Head on back without me.
I think I'll stay up here a bit longer.
Daiki.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Ninako, I sort of want to be alone right now...
Sayuri?
What, came to poke fun at the rejected guy?
You know, I thought sticking you two together
would finally get me to give up.
But I see it doesn't work that way at all.
Just because my crush loves someone else,
doesn't mean my feelings will disappear.
Isn't that right?
Huh?
W-Wait, what?
Surprised?
I have a crush on someone.
Have this seat.
- Thank you.
- No problem, I get off at the next stop.
This love of mine will never come to fruition.
Guess we took the same train again.
Looks like it.
I feel my chest squeeze.
I feel the suffocation.
I feel the tearfulness.
And I feel the pain,
like something is stabbing through my heart, too.
What are you smirking about?
Huh?
I wasn't smirking.
Don't lie, I saw you smiling.
Let's just say, it's nothing.
What's that supposed to mean?
Weirdo.
I'm glad someone like Ren...
is my first crush.
See you.
I didn't fall for him, hoping anything would come out of this.
I just like him.
And I want to tell him.
Ren!
I want him to know how happy I am to be in love.
That's all.
What's up?
Ren.
I...
I like you.
[What's in store, on STROBE EDGE]
Every time our eyes meet,
I fall for him more and more.
That's just so stupid.
What an interesting girl.
You can't expect anything from Ren
so long as he has a girlfriend.
When you have a crush like mine, it'll become obvious, Ando.
Doesn't it bother you that I keep crushing on Ninako?
You're not being fair to me right now.
Nothing wrong with finding a new side to yourself.
You're such a weirdo, Kinoshita.
I've discovered another reason to like him.
[Epilogue]
- Oh my gosh, isn't this so cute?
- My, it's so adorable!
Put that on your bag, and you'd start a trend.
- You think?
- Absolutely.
- I think I'm getting it.
- You totally should!